andrerieu.com 2017-06-26

# Terms and conditions / privacy policy - The official André Rieu website

* * *

PRIVACY POLICY ANDRÉ RIEU PRODUCTIONS B.V.

Please read our Privacy Policy carefully, as it states in which way and for which purposes we gather personal data. By submitting your personal data to us, you grant us permission to process and transfer your personal data as described in this Privacy Policy.

1.    Administration and purposes data processing

1.1.       André Rieu Productions BV (hereafter: "ARP") - also trading as André Rieu Travel - respects the privacy of the visitors of its websites [www.andrerieu.com](http://www.andrerieu.com/) and [www.travel.andrerieu.com](http://www.travel.andrerieu.com/) (hereafter jointly and separately: "the website") and ensures that personal information you submit to us will be treated confidentially. Processing of personal data is carried out in agreement with the requirements set by the Dutch Personal Data Protection Act. ARP is the 'responsible party' for processing personal data, as meant in the applicable European or non-European regulatory framework.

1.2.       USE

ARP uses the information gathered for the following purposes:

-       If you make an order in our online shop, ARP needs your name, email address, delivery address and payment data to process your order and to keep you informed of its progress;

-       If you order a travel package or day trip on [www.travel.andrerieu.com](http://www.travel.andrerieu.com/), ARP needs your Christian names, family name, birth place and date, nationality, email address, address and details of your identification in order to perform the travel package or day trip and to keep you informed of its progress;

-       If you take part in a campaign or contest, ARP needs your name, address and email address to execute the campaign or contest;

-       In order for you to comfortably shop in our online shop or book a travel package or day trip, we use your permission to save your personal data and details regarding your order and the use of our services. This allows us to personalize the website;

-       To send you messages regarding your transactions and the events you visited;

-       To monitor and improve our products, services and websites;

-       To prevent illegal behaviour or safeguard legal rights and for protective reasons within the boundaries of legal frameworks in force.

-       To enable activities aimed at increasing our customer database.

1.3.       NEWSLETTER

ARP offers a newsletter in which ARP wants to inform those interested about news regarding to the artist André Rieu and/or ARP's activities in the broadest sense, its services and related issues. Your email address will only be added to our subscription list after your explicit permission (opt in). Each newsletter contains a link to unsubscribe (opt out);

1.4.       CONTESTS

If you respond to a campaign or contest, ARP needs the data mentioned in 1.2 to execute the campaign, to publish the winner or winners and/or to measure the response to its marketing promotion.

1.5.       REVIEWS

If you decide to write a review, you may choose to include your name and other personal data. ARP values your opinion, but reserves the right not to publish or to remove reviews that do not comply with ARP's website terms of use or which are of a defamatory character.

1.6.       WEBSITE

The website records general visitor's data. In this respect, particularly your computer's IP address, any login name, the time of the data requests and any information your browser sends along with a visit may be registered and used for statistical analysis of visiting and clicking behaviour on the website. This also allows ARP to optimize the performance of the website.

1.7.       THIRD PARTIES

ARP will not sell your personal details to third parties, but will, however, make your details available to third parties that are involved in the processing of your order or booking. ARP obliges its employees and third parties engaged by ARP to respect confidentiality of your data.

1.8.       ACCESS AND REMOVAL

You can change or remove - or have removed - your personal details by informing ARP. You have the legal right to request us to inform you of how we have recorded your personal details and if so, to request us to provide you with a report of these personal details. In case you would like to make use of your rights as the involved party to access your data, please contact us. However, we require from you to supply us with sufficient information to verify your identity and to send you the report. We reserve the right to charge you the legally permitted amount for sending you your personal details. We will send you the requested information within four weeks after receipt of your request.

2.    Payment details

2.1.       ARP will do its utmost to ensure proper safety of your payment details.

2.2.       TICKETS

If you order or buy a ticket for an ARP event or an event organised by ARP, ARP receives your name, email address, delivery address and information about your order from Paylogic Nederland BV (an organization independent of ARP that processes ticketing and ticket payment through the Internet). The details you have to provide for payment will also be available to PayLogic Nederland BV, that will only use the data for the purpose of processing your payment. Paylogic Nederland BV acts on behalf of ARP as the processor of these details. For more information about how Paylogic Nederland BV processes your personal details, we refer you to Paylogic Nederland's Privacy Policy , which (also) applies to your order or purchase.

2.3.       ONLINE SHOP AND PACKAGES

The following applies to payment for products in the online shop and for travel packages and/or day trips:

-       PAYMENTS

Payments - except credit card payments - will be processed by the (website of) Ogone Payment Services, an organization indepedent of ARP that processes payments through the internet. Details you need to provide for payment will become available to Ogone Payment Services, that will use such data solely for the purposes of processing payments. Ogone Payment Services will provide the data only to the organization selected by you for payment. Ogone Payment Services  acts on behalf of  ARP as the processor of these details. For more information about how Ogone Payment Services processes your personal details, we refer you to Ogone Payment Services' Privacy Policy , which applies to your payments.

-       CREDIT CARD

In case you select payment of ARP's products or services by

credit card, payments will be processed by (the website of) Paysquare BV, an organization independent of ARP that processes payments through the internet. Details you need to provide for payment will become available to Paysquare BV, that will use such data solely for the purposes of processing payments. Paysquare BV will provide the data only to the organization selected by you for payment. Paysquare BV acts on behalf of ARP as the processor of these details. For more information about how Paysquare BV processes your personal details, we refer you to Paysquare's Privacy Policy , which applies to your credit card payments.

3.       Google Analytics

3.1.       ARP uses Google Analytics, a website traffic analysis tool offered by Google Inc. ("Google") to track how users make use of the website and to monitor the effectiveness of ARP's Adwords advertisements on Google's search pages. Information obtained in this way, including your computer's address (IP address) is being transferred to Google and saved on Google's servers. For more information about how Google and Google Analytics process your personal details, we refer to you Google's Privacy Policy and Google Analytics' Privacy Policy.

3.2.       Google uses this information to track how ARP's website is being used, to provide ARP with reports about the website and to offer its advertisers information about the effectiveness of their campaigns. Google may provide this information to third parties in case Google is legally forced to do so, or in case third parties process data on behalf of Google. ARP has no say in this. ARP has permitted Google to use the information about ARP's website obtained through Google Analytics for other Google services.

4.    Use of cookies

In order to be of better service, ARP uses so-called 'cookies' to improve analysis of how visitors use our website. Cookies are small bits of information that your browser saves on your computer. ARP uses cookies to be able to recognise you in a future visit to our website. Cookies enable ARP to gather information about the use of its services and to improve and adjusts its services to the needs of its users. Our cookies contain information to identify persons. When you visit our website, you expressly agree with the use of cookies. You can configure your computer not to receive cookies from ARP during your visit to the website (privacy settings). However, this may mean that you cannot make use of all facilities of our website.

5.    Facebook and Twitter

5.1.       Our website contains buttons to promote or share pages on social networks such as, but not restricted to, Facebook and Twitter. These buttons are executed by bits of software code provided by Facebook and Twitter. Among other things, these codes put cookies on your computer.

5.2.       ARP advises you to read Facebook's and Twitter's privacy statements - which may change regularly, which statements (also) apply in case the user of our website clicks on the corresponding buttons.

6.    Liability

We attach great value to securing the safety of your personal details. We use several safety techniques and procedures to protect your personal details against unauthorized access and use, however, no foolproof system exists. Therefore we cannot warrant complete safety of our database. Nor can we warrant that data submitted by you has not been intercepted during transfer via the Internet. All transfer of data is at your own risk. In case of interception of your personal details or unauthorized access or unauthorized use of our database, we are neither liable nor responsible for any resulting improper use of your personal details. Neither do we accept responsibility or liability for transactions which fall under the privacy provisions, terms of use and/or other general terms and conditions of third parties mentioned in this Privacy Policy, nor do we accept responsibility or liability for loss or damages resulting from the use of services from these third parties.

7.    Amendment privacy statement

7.1.       ARP reserves the right to make amendments to the Privacy Policy described in this document. We will clearly indicate on our website any amendments made. If you continue to use our website after we have given notice of amendment, you state to agree with the amended Privacy Policy.

7.2.       ARP advises you to regularly check our Privacy Policy for any amendments.

7.3.       This Privacy Policy was last amended in October 2013.

For any questions regarding our Privacy Policy, click here to contact us.
